Guide to the Arthur H. Landis Oral History Collection ALBA AUDIO 066
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Audiocassettes. (NOTE: Stored with other ALBA audio-cassette collections.)
  - Van Clute, Wilton; Nick (Mike) Pappas; Kenneth Shaker; and Ruby Kaufman Interviews, undated (Item 66- 95)
  - Van Clute, Wilton; Nick (Mike) Pappas; Kenneth Shaker; and Steve Nelson Interviews, undated (Item 66- 96)
  - Colow, Maury; and Milton Wolff Interviews (I), undated (Item 66- 97)
  - Colow, Maury; and Milton Wolff Interviews (II), undated (Item 66- 98)
  - Colow, Maury; and Milton Wolff Interviews (III), undated (Item 66- 99)
  - Davidow, Ruth; George Foucek; [Donald MacLeod?]; [Donald Thayer?]; and [Wilbur Ed Wellman?] Interviews, undated (Item 66- 101)
  - Eider, Louis Interview, undated (Item 66- 102)
  - Eider, Louis; Fred Keller; and Abraham Osheroff Interviews, undated (Item 66- 103)
  - Foucek, George; Sidney Levine; [Donald MacLeod?]; Donald Thayer; Steve Nelson; Charles Nusser; and Harold Smith Interviews, undated (Item 66- 104)
  - Foucek, George; Sidney Levine; [Donald MacLeod?]; and Donald Thayer Interviews (I), undated (Item 66- 105)
  - Foucek, George; Sidney Levine; [Donald MacLeod?]; and Donald Thayer Interviews (II), undated (Item 66- 106)
  - Foucek, George; Sidney Levine; [Donald MacLeod?]; Donald Thayer; Fred Keller; and Abraham Osheroff Interviews, undated (Item 66- 107)
  - Foucek, George; [Donald MacLeod?]; Donald Thayer; and Wilbur Ed Wellman Interviews, undated (Item 66- 108)
  - Foucek, George; Sidney Levine; Donald McClould (?); and Donald Thayer Interviews, undated (Item 66- 109)
  - Geiser, Carl Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 110)
  - Geiser, Carl Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 111)
  - Goddard, Howard; and Evelyn Hutchins Interviews, undated (Item 66- 112)
  - Goddard, Howard; and Evelyn Hutchins Interviews with Remarks on Book, undated (Item 66- 113)
  - Goddard, Howard; and [Gabriel Quinones?] Interviews, undated (Item 66- 114)
  - Goff, Irving; and Harold Smith Interviews (I), undated (Item 66- 115)
  - Goff, Irving; and Harold Smith Interviews (II), undated (Item 66- 116)
  - Goldstein, Benjamin; and Irving Goff Interviews (I), undated (Item 66- 117)
  - Goldstein, Benjamin; and Irving Goff Interviews (II), undated (Item 66- 118)
  - Grodden, Daniel Interview, undated (Item 66- 119)
  - Grodden, Daniel; Herman Klein; and Max Robert Klonsky Interviews, undated (Item 66- 120)
  - Keller, Fred Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 121)
  - Keller, Fred Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 122)
  - Keller, Fred; Steve Nelson; Charles Nusser; Harold Smith Interviews, undated (Item 66- 123)
  - Keller, Fred; Abraham Osheroff Interviews, undated (Item 66- 124)
  - Klein, Herman "Gabby" Interview, undated (Item 66- 125)
  - Klein, Herman; Arthur Landis; Robert Klonsky; and Donald Thayer Interviews, undated (Item 66- 126)
  - Klein, Herman; Charles Nusser; and Robert Klonsky Interviews, undated (Item 66- 127)
  - Klein, Herman; Charles Nusser; Robert Klonsky; and Unknown Interviews, undated (Item 66- 128)
  - Klein, Herman; and Louis Zlotnick Interviews, undated (Item 66- 129)
  - Levine, Sidney; and Donald Thayer Interviews, undated (Item 66- 130)
  - MacLeod, Donald; Steve Nelson; Charles Nusser; and Harold Smith Interviews, undated (Item 66- 131)
  - MacLeod, Donald; and Yale Stuart Interviews, undated (Item 66- 132)
  - MacLeod, Donald; Donald Thayer; and Wilbur Ed Wellman Interviews (I), undated (Item 66- 133)
  - MacLeod, Donald; Donald Thayer; and Wilbur Ed Wellman Interviews (II), undated (Item 66- 134)
  - McNeil, Allan Interview, undated (Item 66- 135)
  - Mundy, Arthur Interview, undated (Item 66- 136)
  - Nelson, Steve Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 137)
  - Nelson, Steve Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 138)
  - Nelson, Steve; and Charles Nusser Interviews, undated (Item 66- 139)
  - Nelson, Steve; Charles Nusser; and Harold Smith Interviews (I), undated (Item 66- 140)
  - Nelson, Steve; Charles Nusser; and Harold Smith Interviews (II), undated (Item 66- 141)
  - Nelson, Steve; and William Sennett Interviews, undated (Item 66- 142)
  - Nusser, Charles; Louis Secundy; and Louis Zlotnick Interviews, undated (Item 66- 143)
  - Parker, Max Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 144)
  - Parker, Max Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 145)
  - Schulman, Rebecca Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 146)
  - Schulman, Rebecca Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 147)
  - Sennett, William Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 148)
  - Sennett, William Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 149)
  - Smith, Harold Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 150)
  - Smith, Harold Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 151)
  - Stuart, Yale Interview, undated (Item 66- 152)
  - Stuart, Yale (Family) Interview, undated (Item 66- 153)
  - Taft, Anne Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 154)
  - Taft, Anne Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 155)
  - Tiven, Isadore Interview (I), undated (Item 66- 156)
  - Tiven, Isadore Interview (II), undated (Item 66- 157)
  - Unknown Interviewee (I), undated (Item 66- 158)
  - Unknown Interviewee (II), undated (Item 66- 159)
  - Unknown Interviewee (III), undated (Item 66-160)